Hello, everyone.
大家好。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到 EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我叫 Marco。
And I'm Erica.
我是 Erica。
And today, we're bringing you another great advanced lesson for all those advanced users
今天，我们为所有高级用户带来另一节很棒的高级课程，
out there.
给那些高级用户。
That's right.
没错。
This is a really, really useful lesson for all of our advanced users.
这对我们所有高级用户来说都是一节非常非常有用的课程。
Exactly.
正是如此。
You asked for a lesson about job interviews and well, here we are.
你们要求一节关于求职面试的课程，好吧，我们来了。
We're bringing you the first of three parts of the job interview series.
我们为你带来求职面试系列三部分中的第一部分。
All right.
好的。
So you said it is the first of three parts.
所以你说这是三部分中的第一部分。
So tell me, what are these three parts?
那么告诉我，这三部分是什么？
Okay.
好的。
In this lesson, we're going to be looking at preparing for a job interview.
在这节课中，我们将探讨如何为求职面试做准备。
So everything you got to do before the job interview.
也就是面试前你需要做的一切。
Part two will be talking about your education, your background, your work experience.
第二部分将讨论你的教育背景、背景和工作经验。
And in part three, we'll take a look at some of the common questions that are asked at
在第三部分中，我们将看看一些常见的面试问题，
a job interview.
在求职面试中。
And so we'll talk about some great ways to answer these questions.
然后我们会讨论一些回答这些问题的好方法。
Exactly.
正是如此。
And these three lessons will be coming out over the next month or so.
这三节课将在未来一个月左右陆续推出。
Exactly.
正是如此。
So we're going to be looking at part one today.
所以今天我们来看第一部分。
So let's take a look at some vocabulary preview.
那么让我们先看一下词汇预览。
Vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
Well, we have three words here in vocabulary preview that you'll hear in the dialogue in
嗯，在词汇预览中，我们有三个词，你会在接下来的对话中听到，
a moment.
马上。
And the first one is actually not really a word, but an acronym.
第一个其实不是一个词，而是一个缩写。
Right.
对。
CRM.
CRM。
So Marco, you are our marketing guy.
所以 Marco，你是我们的营销专家。
Tell us, what is a CRM?
告诉我们，什么是 CRM？
Well, it's really common in marketing.
嗯，这在营销中很常见。
It stands for customer relationship management.
它代表客户关系管理。
Okay.
好的。
Or customer relation management.
或者客户关系管理。
But basically it's the relationship that the company has with its customers.
但基本上就是公司与客户之间的关系。
Okay.
好的。
So CRM basically has parts like feedback or customer support, problems that they might
所以 CRM 基本上包括反馈、客户支持、他们可能遇到的问题，
have, and also information about habits and likes and dislikes from their customers or
以及关于客户或用户习惯、喜好和厌恶的信息。
users.
用户。
Okay.
好的。
But I commonly hear this word used as a noun.
但我经常听到这个词被用作名词。
So something like, can you check in the CRM?
比如，你能查一下 CRM 吗？
Right.
对。
There is some software out there that's called the CRM.
有一些软件叫做 CRM。
So SugarCRM or many different softwares, which basically manages your database of customers.
比如 SugarCRM 或许多不同的软件，它们基本上管理你的客户数据库。
Basically software that englobes this whole thing.
基本上是涵盖这一切的软件。
Okay.
好的。
Got it.
明白了。
All right.
好的。
Our next phrase in vocabulary preview.
词汇预览中的下一个短语。
Custom designed.
定制设计。
So when something is custom designed, it means it's a special design just for you.
所以当某物是定制设计时，意味着它是专门为你设计的特殊设计。
So it's unique.
所以它是独一无二的。
Right.
对。
That's what the word custom means.
这就是 custom 这个词的意思。
Unique.
独一无二的。
Like made especially for one person.
像是专门为一个人制作的。
Right.
对。
So you have custom designed or also custom made.
所以你有定制设计或定制制作。
You see that a lot, for example, in cars, right?
你经常看到这个，比如在汽车上，对吧？
A custom made car.
一辆定制汽车。
Yes.
是的。
Or maybe a custom built house.
或者可能是定制建造的房子。
A custom built house.
定制建造的房子。
Yep.
是的。
With your specific likes and dislikes.
根据你具体的喜好和厌恶。
Yeah.
是的。
Your requirements.
你的要求。
Yep.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
And our last word, core values.
最后一个词，核心价值观。
Core values.
核心价值观。
So the core values of a company.
所以公司的核心价值观。
What does the core mean, actually?
core 到底是什么意思？
The center.
中心。
The center, right?
中心，对吧？
Yep.
是的。
So in here, I think it's like the center or the most important.
所以在这里，我认为它指的是中心或最重要的。
The most important things the company believes in, right?
公司信仰的最重要的事情，对吧？
Right.
对。
So maybe respect for the environment.
比如尊重环境。
Okay.
好的。
Or developing their employees.
或者培养员工。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Okay.
好的。
So the core values.
所以是核心价值观。
Yep.
是的。
The main things that the company believes in.
公司信仰的主要事情。
A great phrase for job interviews.
求职面试中一个很好的短语。
Oh, yes.
哦，是的。
Very good phrase.
非常好的短语。
Okay.
好的。
So why don't we listen to a dialogue.
那么我们为什么不听一段对话呢？
Erica, what exactly is happening?
Erica，到底发生了什么？
All right.
好的。
We're going to be listening to two friends.
我们将听到两个朋友。
And this guy is getting ready to go on a job interview.
这个家伙正准备去参加求职面试。
So his friend is helping him to prepare.
所以他的朋友在帮他准备。
Okay.
好的。
So let's go over everything one more time.
那么让我们再复习一遍所有内容。
I really want you to get this job.
我真的很想让你得到这份工作。
I know.
我知道。
It's an amazing growth opportunity.
这是一个绝佳的发展机会。
They're true industry leaders.
他们是真正的行业领导者。
And it would be so interesting to be part of an organization that is the undisputed
成为这个无可争议的领导者组织的一员会非常有趣，
leader in business process platform development.
在业务流程平台开发方面。
So let's see.
那么让我们看看。
You did your research on the company, right?
你做了关于公司的研究，对吧？
Well, I visited the website and read up on what they do.
嗯，我访问了网站并阅读了他们做什么。
They're an IT service company that offers comprehensive business solutions for large
他们是一家 IT 服务公司，为大型企业提供全面的业务解决方案。
corporations.
大型企业。
They provide services such as CRM development, and they also offer custom designed applications.
他们提供诸如 CRM 开发等服务，还提供定制设计的应用程序。
So what would be your role in the company?
那么你在公司中的角色是什么？
Well, the position is for an account manager.
嗯，职位是客户经理。
That basically means that I would be the link between our clients and our development team.
这基本上意味着我将是客户和我们开发团队之间的纽带。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
And so why do you want to work with them?
那么你为什么想和他们一起工作？
Well, as I said, they're the industry leaders.
嗯，正如我所说，他们是行业领导者。
They have a really great growth strategy, amazing development opportunities for employees.
他们有一个非常好的增长战略，为员工提供惊人的发展机会。
And it seems like they have a strong corporate governance.
而且他们似乎有强大的公司治理。
They're all about helping companies grow and unleashing potential.
他们致力于帮助公司成长和释放潜力。
I guess their core values and mission really resonated with me.
我想他们的核心价值观和使命真的引起了我的共鸣。
Oh, and they offer a six week vacation, stock options and bonuses.
哦，他们还提供六周假期、股票期权和奖金。
I'm totally going to cash in on that.
我绝对要从中捞一笔。
You idiot.
你这个白痴。
You don't say that.
你不能那么说。
Do you want this job or not?
你到底想不想要这份工作？
All right, so he was doing great, but in the end, he said something he shouldn't, right?
好的，所以他之前表现很好，但最后他说了不该说的话，对吧？
Yeah, I don't think talking about money as your primary motivation for coming on to a
是的，我认为把金钱作为你加入新公司的主要动机并不是正确的方式。
new company is really the way to go.
新公司。
Yeah, and we're going to talk about that a little bit later, but let's take a look real
是的，我们稍后会讨论这个，但让我们快速看一下语言要点。
quick at some language takeaway.
语言要点。
Language takeaway.
All right, in this lesson, we have five key words for you from the dialogue, which we
好的，在这节课中，我们从对话中为你准备了五个关键词，
hope that you will remember.
我们希望你能记住。
Let's take a look at the first one.
让我们看看第一个。
Undisputed.
无可争议的。
So, this is kind of a strange word.
所以，这有点奇怪的一个词。
Let's listen to some examples before we explain it.
在我们解释之前，先听一些例子。
Example one.
例子一。
It's undisputed that she's the best person for the job.
无可争议的是，她是这份工作的最佳人选。
Example two.
例子二。
The undisputed truth is that unemployment is rising.
无可争议的事实是失业率在上升。
No one doubts that.
没有人怀疑这一点。
Example three.
例子三。
She's the undisputed champion of the world.
她是世界无可争议的冠军。
Well, I can understand from these examples that it means there is no doubt.
嗯，从这些例子中我能理解它意味着没有疑问。
There is no doubt.
没有疑问。
There's no question.
没有问题。
Okay, now let's take a look at our second word, growth opportunity.
好的，现在让我们看看第二个词，发展机会。
Growth opportunity.
发展机会。
It's a great growth opportunity.
这是一个很好的发展机会。
So it's an excellent chance to improve, right?
所以这是一个提升自己的绝佳机会，对吧？
To improve professionally and also on a personal side, right?
在职业上和个人方面提升，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
So, when we talk about growth opportunities, we can also use the phrase a development opportunity.
所以当我们谈论发展机会时，我们也可以使用短语“发展机会”。
And it's the same thing, right?
这是同样的意思，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
To develop, to grow.
去发展，去成长。
To improve yourself.
提升自己。
Okay.
好的。
Now, let's take a look at our third word, read up.
现在，让我们看看第三个词，研读。
Read up.
研读。
So, when you read up on something.
所以当你研读某物时。
Well, obviously, you read it, right?
嗯，显然，你阅读它，对吧？
Right.
对。
But you're reading it specifically for some information so you can know more about the
但你是专门为了获取某些信息而阅读，以便了解更多关于这个主题。
subject.
这个主题。
So, it's kind of similar to study, right?
所以它有点像学习，对吧？
Kind of.
有点。
But really with the idea that you're trying to improve your knowledge about a particular
但真正强调的是你试图提高自己在特定领域的知识。
field.
领域。
Okay.
好的。
Now, for our fourth word, unleash potential.
现在，第四个词，释放潜力。
Unleash potential.
释放潜力。
Okay.
好的。
So, to unleash.
所以，释放。
All right.
好的。
Well, I'm going to paint a picture for you.
嗯，我来给你描绘一个画面。
All right.
好的。
So, imagine you have your dog, right?
想象你有一条狗，对吧？
And your dog is walking on a leash.
你的狗正拴着狗绳走路。
Like it has a string or a rope attached to it.
就像它身上系着一根绳子或绳索一样。
Right.
对。
So, then when you undo the leash, you unleash the dog.
所以，当你解开狗绳时，你就把狗放开了。
And then what happens?
然后会发生什么？
It goes around and it's running.
它到处跑，四处奔跑。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
对对对。
It's going everywhere.
它到处乱跑。
So, if you unleash potential, you release it and let it go and help it grow and become
所以，如果你释放潜力，你就把它放出来，让它自由发展，帮助它成长并变得
bigger.
更大。
Yes.
是的。
Exactly.
没错。
So, you give it freedom.
所以，你给了它自由。
So, potential is the capabilities or abilities that a person has, right?
那么，潜力就是一个人拥有的能力或才干，对吧？
Yes.
是的。
To do something great.
去做一些了不起的事情。
Okay.
好的。
Unleash potential.
释放潜力。
This, I think, is an excellent word to use in a job interview.
我认为，这个词在求职面试中非常有用。
I think it is really descriptive and really powerful.
我觉得它非常形象，也很有力量。
Yeah, it is.
是的，确实如此。
Yeah.
嗯。
It's a good word.
这是个好词。
Okay.
好的。
So, let's go to the last one now.
那么，现在我们来看最后一个。
Resonate with.
引起共鸣。
So, he mentioned, this really resonated with me.
他提到，这真的让我产生了共鸣。
So, what does he mean by resonated?
那么，他说的“共鸣”是什么意思？
I guess he means it connected to him, right?
我猜他的意思是这与他产生了联系，对吧？
It touched him.
它触动了他。
So, he agrees with this idea or he feels that he can relate to it.
所以，他同意这个想法，或者他觉得能与之产生关联。
Yeah, exactly.
是的，没错。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I think this one needs a few examples to really show its meaning.
我觉得这个词需要几个例子才能真正说明它的含义。
Okay.
好的。
Let's listen.
我们来听一下。
Example 1.
例子1。
The candidate's speech really resonated with the voters.
候选人的演讲真的引起了选民的共鸣。
Example 2.
例子2。
Their music doesn't really resonate with me.
他们的音乐并没有真正引起我的共鸣。
Example 3.
例子3。
Their commitment to fight global warming resonates with me.
他们对抗全球变暖的承诺让我产生了共鸣。
All right.
好了。
So, it's clear now to resonate with, right?
那么，现在“引起共鸣”的意思清楚了吧？
Okay.
好的。
So, why don't we go and listen to our dialogue for the last time and then we'll come back
那么，我们最后再听一遍对话，然后回来
and give you some great pointers about preparing for a job interview.
给你一些关于准备求职面试的好建议。
Okay.
好的。
So let's go over everything one more time.
那么，我们再来过一遍所有内容。
I really want you to get this job.
我真的很想让你得到这份工作。
I know.
我知道。
It's an amazing growth opportunity.
这是一个绝佳的成长机会。
They're true industry leaders and it would be so interesting to be part of an organization
他们是真正的行业领导者，能成为这个
that is the undisputed leader in business process platform development.
在业务流程平台开发领域无可争议的领导者组织的一员，会非常有趣。
So let's see.
那么，我们来看看。
You did your research on the company, right?
你做了关于这家公司的研究，对吧？
Well, I visited the website and read up on what they do.
嗯，我访问了他们的网站，并阅读了他们所做的工作。
They're an IT service company that offers comprehensive business solutions for large
他们是一家IT服务公司，为大型
corporations.
企业提供全面的商业解决方案。
They provide services such as CRM development and they also offer custom designed applications.
他们提供CRM开发等服务，还提供定制设计的应用程序。
So what would be your role in the company?
那么，你在公司里的角色是什么？
Well, the position is for an account manager.
嗯，这个职位是客户经理。
That basically means that I would be the link between our clients and our development team.
基本上意味着我将成为客户和我们开发团队之间的桥梁。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
And so why do you want to work with them?
那你为什么想和他们一起工作？
Well, as I said, they're the industry leaders.
嗯，正如我所说，他们是行业领导者。
They have a really great growth strategy, amazing development opportunities for employees,
他们有一个非常好的增长战略，为员工提供极好的发展机会，
and it seems like they have a strong corporate governance.
而且他们似乎有强大的公司治理。
They're all about helping companies grow and unleashing potential.
他们致力于帮助公司成长和释放潜力。
I guess their core values and mission really resonated with me.
我想他们的核心价值观和使命真的引起了我的共鸣。
Oh, and they offer six weeks vacation, stock options and bonuses.
哦，他们还提供六周假期、股票期权和奖金。
I'm totally going to cash in on that.
我绝对要好好利用这些。
You idiot.
你这个白痴。
You don't say that.
你不能那么说。
Do you want this job or not?
你到底想不想要这份工作？
OK, so preparing for a job interview is really important, right?
好的，所以准备求职面试非常重要，对吧？
Yes.
是的。
Yeah.
嗯。
And we're going to give you some really basic tips about how you can prepare for a job interview.
我们将给你一些关于如何准备求职面试的基本建议。
Yeah.
嗯。
I got to confess something to you, Marco.
我得跟你坦白一件事，Marco。
What?
什么？
I love job interviews.
我喜欢求职面试。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah, I know it's really weird.
是的，我知道这很奇怪。
Most people hate them, but I love them.
大多数人讨厌它们，但我喜欢。
So you love being the interviewer or going to job interviews?
所以你喜欢当面试官还是去参加面试？
Both.
两者都喜欢。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
I like everything about them.
我喜欢关于它们的一切。
So I feel like I have a lot of passion to share with you about this.
所以我觉得我有很多热情可以和你分享。
All right.
好的。
So let's take a look at the first point or the first tip that you can help us out with.
那么，我们来看看第一个要点或第一个你可以帮我们的建议。
So before you go to a job interview, you should do a little bit of research, right?
所以，在你去求职面试之前，你应该做一些研究，对吧？
Right.
对。
And that's our first point.
这就是我们的第一点。
It's really important to know as much as you can about the company, their history, their
尽可能多地了解公司、他们的历史、
product, their management style, just as much information as you can find out about how
产品、管理风格，以及你能找到的关于他们
they work and what they do.
如何工作和做什么的所有信息，这非常重要。
And why do you think this is important?
你为什么认为这很重要？
Well basically, you'll be asked about it in the interview.
基本上，面试中你会被问到这些问题。
Right.
对。
And so if you show that you haven't prepared, you haven't done any research, you show that
所以，如果你表现出没有准备、没有做任何研究，你就表明
you don't care.
你不在乎。
One of the best ways that you can impress in a job interview is to show that you know
在求职面试中给人留下深刻印象的最佳方法之一就是展示你了解
about the company, important things like you know what kind of products they offer or what's
公司的重要信息，比如你知道他们提供什么产品或
their largest market.
他们最大的市场是什么。
And I guess that really impresses the interviewer because it shows that you are interested in
我想这真的会给面试官留下深刻印象，因为这表明你对这家公司感兴趣，
this company and they really want the job.
并且你真的想要这份工作。
And that you are willing to do the extra work it takes to prepare yourself.
而且你愿意付出额外的努力来准备自己。
Because I think that will show the interviewer that later on when you're working for them,
因为我认为这会向面试官表明，以后当你为他们工作时，
you'll do that extra work on the job.
你会在工作中付出额外的努力。
Exactly.
没错。
That's a really good point.
这说得很好。
So that's our first point, our first tip, to do some research.
所以这是我们的第一点，第一个建议，就是做一些研究。
Yes.
是的。
Now you've done your research.
现在你已经做了研究。
You know everything about the company.
你了解了公司的一切。
What else should you do?
你还应该做什么？
Once you've read up on the company, you've got to spend some time thinking about yourself.
一旦你了解了公司，你就需要花一些时间思考自己。
You've got to prepare to sell yourself to the company.
你必须准备好向公司推销自己。
So to sell yourself, to really demonstrate them why you are the perfect person for the
所以，推销自己，真正向他们展示为什么你是这份工作的
job.
完美人选。
Right.
对。
Because a lot of people think about why they want to work for the company, right?
因为很多人会想为什么他们想为这家公司工作，对吧？
Because they feel like they're aligned with the core values or the message of the company
因为他们觉得自己与公司的核心价值观一致，或者公司的
resonates with them.
信息引起了他们的共鸣。
But what the interviewer really wants to hear is how you, the interviewee, is going to benefit
但面试官真正想听的是你，作为面试者，将如何
the company.
使公司受益。
What are you going to bring to the company?
你会给公司带来什么？
Right.
对。
And this is the most important part, is to know what are your skills, right?
而这是最重要的部分，就是要知道你的技能是什么，对吧？
Yes.
是的。
And it's not enough to just say, well, I am a great leader.
仅仅说“我是一个伟大的领导者”是不够的。
Yeah.
嗯。
Right.
对。
So if you are a great leader, you should be ready to give an example of how you have demonstrated
所以，如果你是一个伟大的领导者，你应该准备好举一个例子，说明你如何表现出
to be a great leader.
自己是一个伟大的领导者。
Yes.
是的。
All right.
好的。
So maybe like an example like, I'm a really strong leader because in my previous job,
所以也许可以举一个例子，比如：“我是一个非常强的领导者，因为在我之前的工作中，
I had the best JD Power ratings for employee satisfaction.
我在员工满意度方面获得了最高的JD Power评级。”
Okay.
好的。
So you're actually showing with numbers or with facts that you are a great leader.
所以，你实际上是用数字或事实来证明你是一个伟大的领导者。
Yeah.
嗯。
So the key thing here, I think, is identify what your strengths and skills are.
所以，我认为关键是要确定你的优势和技能是什么。
Think of specific examples.
想出具体的例子。
If you can, give numbers and show how you can bring this skill and your experiences
如果可以，给出数字，并展示你如何将这项技能和你的经验
to the new company.
带到新公司。
And now, well, you're ready to sell yourself.
现在，你已经准备好推销自己了。
You've done your research.
你已经做了研究。
Now you have all of these things in your mind.
现在你脑子里有所有这些事情。
You have to practice.
你必须练习。
Yes.
是的。
Right.
对。
A much overlooked stage in the preparation.
这是准备过程中经常被忽视的一个阶段。
Yeah.
嗯。
A lot of people think it through.
很多人只是想一想。
They write things down, but don't really practice.
他们写下来，但并没有真正练习。
Yeah.
嗯。
So I know you have a few tips about how you can practice interviewing effectively.
所以我知道你有一些关于如何有效练习面试的建议。
Okay.
好的。
Well, the first thing that you should do is use your friends.
嗯，你应该做的第一件事就是利用你的朋友。
Yeah.
嗯。
Right.
对。
They got to be good for something.
他们总得有点用处。
Exactly.
没错。
And well, probably your friends are also working at a company.
嗯，可能你的朋友也在某家公司工作。
Maybe they're managers, or maybe they've interviewed someone before already.
也许他们是经理，或者他们以前面试过别人。
So you can set up a mini interview and have them pretend that they are the interviewer
所以你可以安排一个小型面试，让他们假装是面试官，
and ask you these questions.
问你这些问题。
And you're trying to answer seriously.
然后你认真回答。
And I'm sure that your friends can give you some great feedback.
我相信你的朋友可以给你一些很好的反馈。
Maybe what you did right, maybe what you did wrong.
也许是你做对了什么，也许是你做错了什么。
So that's a really good way.
所以这是一个很好的方法。
And another thing is also you can record yourself.
另一件事是你可以录下自己。
Yes.
是的。
Right.
对。
Yeah.
嗯。
If you have a video camera or even a web, I mean, many people have a webcam like right
如果你有摄像机，甚至网络摄像头，我的意思是，很多人都有网络摄像头，比如就在
in your laptop.
你的笔记本电脑上。
Record yourself actually doing the practice interview with your friends.
录下你和朋友实际进行练习面试的过程。
And this is really useful because you can later see what you recorded and detect some
这非常有用，因为你之后可以看录下的内容，并发现一些
of the things that maybe aren't really useful or good.
可能不太有用或不太好的东西。
You know, for example, posture is a really important aspect.
你知道，例如，姿势是一个非常重要的方面。
So what do you mean posture?
你说的姿势是什么意思？
So the way that you are sitting down in your seat.
就是你坐在座位上的方式。
Yep.
嗯。
And how you are expressing yourself with your hands.
以及你如何用手势表达自己。
Yep.
嗯。
Some people, you know, they move a lot during the interview because of course you're nervous.
有些人，你知道，他们在面试中会动来动去，因为你当然会紧张。
So maybe they're moving from side to side or playing with their feet or playing with
所以也许他们会左右摇晃，或者摆弄脚，或者摆弄
something on the table or moving their hands in an awkward way.
桌子上的东西，或者以尴尬的方式移动手。
So those are the things that you have to watch out for.
所以这些是你需要注意的事情。
Yes.
是的。
So I guess it's really important to sit up straight and to show that you are powerful
所以我想坐直并展示出你很有力量非常重要。
and in control.
并且要掌控局面。
And another really great thing is eye contact, right?
另一个非常好的方面是眼神交流，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
We were talking about this earlier.
我们之前讨论过这个。
And why is eye contact so important?
为什么眼神交流这么重要？
If an interviewee maintains eye contact with me for like most of the interview, I feel
如果面试者在大部分面试时间里都和我保持眼神交流，我觉得
like they have really good people skills.
他们的人际交往能力很强。
In my opinion, I would say they have a lot of self-confidence.
在我看来，我会说他们很有自信。
Yeah, I'd agree.
是的，我同意。
Right?
对吧？
Yep.
嗯。
Because if a person is looking down or not looking directly at you, it's either one of
因为如果一个人低头看或者不直视你，在我看来，要么是
two things in my opinion.
两种情况之一。
It's either they are not confident enough with themselves or they are lying to you.
要么是他们对自己不够自信，要么就是在对你撒谎。
Yes.
对。
Right?
对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Or also they just they don't have good people skills.
或者也可能是他们只是不擅长人际交往。
Yeah.
是的。
Which is a problem in today's sort of knowledge-based economy.
这在当今的知识经济时代是个问题。
Exactly.
完全正确。
So it's really important to maintain eye contact.
所以保持眼神交流非常重要。
And one other really important thing related to eye contact posture is the handshake.
另一个与眼神交流和姿态相关的重要方面是握手。
When you get to the interview, it's really, really important to give a firm, good handshake.
当你去面试时，给出一个坚定、良好的握手非常非常重要。
So what qualifies as a firm, good handshake?
那么，什么样的握手才算坚定、良好呢？
Well, you don't have to prove that you are ultra strong, right?
嗯，你不需要证明自己超级强壮，对吧？
So you don't have to squeeze the other person's hand really hard.
所以你不必用力挤压对方的手。
And like break their hand.
就像要捏碎他们的手一样。
Exactly.
完全正确。
It's not like a strength contest.
这不是力量比赛。
No.
不是。
A good firm handshake is squeezing normally, not too tight, not too loose, but your entire
一个好的坚定握手是正常用力，不要太紧，也不要太松，但你的整个
palm, your entire hand has to be in contact with the other person's palm or hand.
手掌，整只手都要与对方的手掌或手接触。
Yes.
对。
Don't give them the fingers, you know, like some people give you only four fingers or
不要只给手指，你知道，有些人只给你四个手指或者
half their hand.
半只手。
Yeah.
是的。
I hate that.
我讨厌那样。
I hate it too.
我也讨厌。
And this goes for men and for women because a lot of women do this.
这对男性和女性都适用，因为很多女性会这样做。
Yeah.
是的。
I call this the dead fish handshake.
我称之为“死鱼式握手”。
It is kind of like a dead fish or the dead hand handshake.
这有点像死鱼或者死手式的握手。
Yeah.
是的。
I absolutely agree with you on this one.
我完全同意你的看法。
So nice firm handshake.
所以要坚定地握手。
Yeah.
是的。
So that's the dead fish handshake and well, these are our tips for preparing for the interview,
这就是死鱼式握手，好了，这些是我们为面试准备的建议，
everything you have to do before it.
面试前需要做的一切。
I'm sure there are a lot more things out there.
我相信还有很多其他事情。
So and I'm sure our users have some insight on this as well.
而且我相信我们的用户对此也有一些见解。
Yeah.
是的。
I'd love to hear it because like I told you, I love job interviews.
我很想听听，因为就像我告诉你的，我喜欢面试。
Yeah.
是的。
So come to our website at EnglishPod.com.
所以请访问我们的网站 EnglishPod.com。
Leave us your comments.
给我们留言评论。
Maybe you've had a good experience with a job interview or maybe a bad one or maybe
也许你在面试中有过好的经历，或者不好的经历，或者也许
even as an interviewer, you've interviewed some really interesting people.
作为面试官，你面试过一些非常有趣的人。
And you've got some great tips to share with us.
并且你有一些很好的技巧可以与我们分享。
Exactly.
完全正确。
So come to our website, leave your questions, leave your comments, share your experiences
所以请访问我们的网站，留下你的问题，留下你的评论，与其他用户分享你的经历
with our other users.
验。
And Erica and I will also be there to participate in the discussion.
我和Erica也会在那里参与讨论。
All right, guys.
好了，各位。
Well, thanks for listening.
嗯，感谢收听。
And until next time, goodbye.
下次再见，拜拜。
Goodbye.
拜拜。